BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- RR Electric - Honolulu, HI, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 136)
- RR Electric - Anderson, IN, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- RR Electric - Indiana, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- RR Electric - Evansville, IN, 1923-1926 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- RR Electric - New Albany, IN, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- RR Electric - Gary, IN, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- RR Electric - Galesburg, IL, 1924-1925 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- RR Electric - Wheaton, IL, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- RR Electric - Bloomington, IL, 1924-1926 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- RR Electric - East St. Louis, IL, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- RR Electric - Granite City, IL, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- RR Electric - Highwood, IL, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- RR Electric - Danville, IL, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- RR Electric - Chicago, IL, 1915-1926 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  1915, 1920, 1923, 1924, 1926
- RR Electric - Aurora, IL, 1926-1927 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- RR Electric - Rockford, IL, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- RR Electric - Peoria, IL, 1921-1927 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  1921, 1926, 1927
- RR Electric - Illinois, 1904-1926 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  1904, 1919, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926
- RR Electric - Chicago, IL, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- RR Electric - Illinois, 1926-1927 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- RR Electric - Cedar Rapids, IA, 1922-1926 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- RR Electric - Davenport, IA, 1919-1926 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- RR Electric - Dubuque, IA, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- RR Electric - Sioux City, IA, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- RR Electric - Des Moines, IA, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- RR Electric - Muscatine, IA, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- RR Electric - Ottumwa, IA, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- RR Electric - Iowa, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- RR Electric - Topeka, KS, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- RR Electric - Bonner Springs, KS, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- RR Electric - Wichita, KS, 1918-1919 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- RR Electric - Kansas, 1924-1926 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- RR Electric - Louisville, KY, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- RR Electric - Kentucky, 1924-1926 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- RR Electric - New Orleans, LA, 1920-1926 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- RR Electric - Lake Charles, LA, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- RR Electric - Shreveport, LA, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- RR Electric - Portland, ME, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- RR Electric - South Portland, ME, 1923-1925 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- RR Electric - Skowhegan, ME, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- RR Electric - Bangor, ME, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- RR Electric - Maine, 1920-1922 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- RR Electric - Baltimore, MD, 1923-1926 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- RR Electric - Boston, MA, 1913-1922 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  1913, 1916, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922
- RR Electric - Boston, MA, 1922-1927 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  1922, 1923, 1925, 1926, 1927
- RR Electric - Worcester, MA, 1905-1924 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- RR Electric - Springfield, MA, 1923-1924 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- RR Electric - Newtonville, MA, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- RR Electric - Holyoke, MA, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- RR Electric - New Bedford, MA, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- RR Electric - Framingham, MA, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- RR Electric - Massachusetts, 1918-1923 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  1918, 1920, 1921, 1923
- RR Electric - Detroit, MI, 1920-1926 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- RR Electric - Grand Rapids, MI, 1923-1925 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- RR Electric - Jackson, MI, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 54)
- RR Electric - Muskegon, MI, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- RR Electric - Saginaw, MI, 1920-1921 (Box 26, Folder 56)
- RR Electric - Michigan, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 57)
- RR Electric - Minneapolis, MN, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 58)
- RR Electric - Duluth, MN, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 59)
- RR Electric - Mexico, MO, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 60)
- RR Electric - St. Louis, MO, 1918-1923 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  1918, 1919, 1922, 1923
- RR Electric - Missouri, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 62)
- RR Electric - Helena, MT, 1919-1922 (Box 26, Folder 63)
- RR Electric - Butte, MT, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 64)
- RR Electric - Omaha, NE, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 65)
- RR Electric - Manchester, NH, 1920-1926 (Box 26, Folder 66)
- RR Electric - Nashua, NH, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 67)
- RR Electric - Atlantic City, NJ, 1918-1923 (Box 26, Folder 68)
- RR Electric - Camden, NJ, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 69)
- RR Electric - Trenton, NJ, 1925-1927 (Box 26, Folder 70)
- RR Electric - New Jersey, 1919-1927 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  1919, 1920, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927
- RR Electric - New York, NY, 1920-1925 (Box 26, Folder 72)
- RR Electric - Rochester, NY, 1922-1924 (Box 26, Folder 73)
- RR Electric - Utica, NY, 1922-1926 (Box 26, Folder 74)
- RR Electric - Newark, NY, 1919-1922 (Box 26, Folder 75)
- RR Electric - Syracuse, NY, 1915-1924 (Box 26, Folder 76)
- RR Electric - Newburgh, NY, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 77)
- RR Electric - Staten Island, NY, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 78)
- RR Electric - Olean, NY, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 79)
- RR Electric - Ossining, NY, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 80)
- RR Electric - Oswego, NY, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 81)
- RR Electric - White Plains, NY, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 82)
- RR Electric - Albany, NY, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 83)
- RR Electric - Auburn, NY, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 84)
- RR Electric - Buffalo, NY, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 85)
- RR Electric - New York, 1919-1925 (Box 26, Folder 86)
  1919, 1920, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925
- RR Electric - Wilmington, NC, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 87)
- RR Electric - Winston Salem, NC, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 88)
- RR Electric - Raleigh, NC, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 89)
- RR Electric - Dayton, OH, 1920-1926 (Box 26, Folder 90)
- RR Electric - Springfield, OH, 1920-1925 (Box 26, Folder 91)
- RR Electric - Toledo, OH, 1917-1927 (Box 26, Folder 92)
  1917, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927
- RR Electric - Elyria, OH, 1905-1926 (Box 26, Folder 93)
  1905, 1923, 1926
- RR Electric - Cincinnati, OH, 1919-1926 (Box 26, Folder 94)
  1919, 1921, 1923, 1924, 1926
- RR Electric - Columbus, OH, 1920-1926 (Box 26, Folder 95)
- RR Electric - Cleveland, OH, 1914-1924 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  1914, 1919, 1920, 1922, 1923, 1924
- RR Electric - Steubenville, OH, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 97)
- RR Electric - Port Clinton, OH, 1924-1926 (Box 26, Folder 98)
- RR Electric - Pomeroy, OH, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 99)
- RR Electric - Mansfield, OH, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 100)
- RR Electric - Findlay, OH, 1923-1925 (Box 26, Folder 101)
- RR Electric - Canton, OH, 1925-1926 (Box 26, Folder 102)
- RR Electric - Akron, OH, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 103)
- RR Electric - Hamilton, OH, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 104)
- RR Electric - Kenmore, OH, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 105)
- RR Electric - Youngstown, OH, 1924-1925 (Box 26, Folder 106)
- RR Electric - Ohio, 1919-1925 (Box 26, Folder 107)
  1919, 1920, 1923, 1924, 1925
- RR Electric - Tulsa, OK, 1923-1926 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- RR Electric - Sapulpa and Tulsa, OK, 1919-1925 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  1919, 1922, 1924, 1925
- RR Electric - Oklahoma City, OK, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- RR Electric - McAlester, OK, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- RR Electric - Oklahoma, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- RR Electric - Portland, OR, 1920-1927 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- RR Electric - Salem, OR, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- RR Electric - Reading, PA, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- RR Electric - Scranton, PA, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- RR Electric - Easton, PA, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- RR Electric - Girardville, PA, 1919-1924 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- RR Electric - York, PA, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- RR Electric - Sharon, PA, 1924-1925 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- RR Electric - Altoona, PA, 1923-1924 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- RR Electric - Dalton, PA, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- RR Electric - Augusta, PA, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- RR Electric - Newton, PA, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- RR Electric - Mauch Chunk, PA, 1919-1922 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- RR Electric - Lansford, PA, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- RR Electric - Jamestown, PA, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- RR Electric - Lehigh Valley, PA, 1920-1923 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- RR Electric - Philadelphia, PA, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- RR Electric - Pittsburgh, PA, 1923-1926 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- RR Electric - Pan Argyll, PA, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- RR Electric - Mars, PA, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- RR Electric - Shamokin, PA, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- RR Electric - Pennsylvania, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- RR Electric - San Juan, PR, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- RR Electric - Providence, RI, 1919-1927 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  1919, 1921, 1922, 1924, 1925, 1927
- RR Electric - Charleston, SC, 1912-1924 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  1912, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1924
- RR Electric - Greenville, SC, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- RR Electric - Spartanburg, SC, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- RR Electric - Memphis, TN, 1920-1925 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925
- RR Electric - Nashville, TN, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- RR Electric - Chattanooga, TN, 1922-1924 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- RR Electric - San Antonio, TX, 1923-1925 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- RR Electric - Dallas, TX, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- RR Electric - Galveston, TX, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- RR Electric - Ogden, UT, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- RR Electric - Salt Lake City, UT, 1917-1923 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- RR Electric - Utah, 1901 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- RR Electric - Virginia, 1919-1928 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  1919, 1920, 1928
- RR Electric - Everett, WA, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- RR Electric - Seattle, WA, 1922-1926 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- RR Electric - Grays Harbor, WA, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- RR Electric - Spokane, WA, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- RR Electric - Milwaukee, WI, 1918-1926 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- RR Electric - Walworth, WI, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- RR Electric - Madison, WI, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- RR Electric - Green Bay, WI, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- RR Electric - Wheeling, WV, 1923-1926 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- RR Electric - Clarksburg, WV, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 52)
- RR Electric - Parkersburg, WV, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- RR Electric - Charleston, WV, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- RR Electric - Cheyenne, WY, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- Board of Arbitration - Springfield, MA (Box 27, Folder 56)
- Courts - United Mine Workers of America and Association of Bituminous Coal Operators of Central PA, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 57)
- Injunction - Tiffany Enameled Brick Co. and Clay Workers of America, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 58)
- Injunction - State of IL and International Broom and Whisk Makers, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 59)
- Injunction - The Charles Stechers Co. and International Association of Machinists, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 60)
- Injunction - American Steel Foundries and Tri-City Trades Council, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 61)
- Strike - Central Trust Co. of NY and International and Great Northern Railway, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 62)
- Electrical Workers - Toledo, OH, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 63)
- Strike Vote - Sailors Union of the Great Lakes, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 64)
- Strike Vote - Brick, Tile, and Terra Cotta Workers, 1903 (Box 27, Folder 65)
- Non-Union Pledge - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific, 1904-1919 (Box 27, Folder 66)
- Metal Polishers - n/a, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 67)
- RR Maintenance of Way - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 68)
- Railway Agents - n/a, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 69)
- Asbestos Workers - International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, 1914-1922 (Box 27, Folder 70)
  1914, 1919, 1922
- Automobile Workers - United Automobile Workers, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Bakers - Bakery and Confectionary Workers International Union, 1906-1926 (Box 27, Folder 72)
  1906, 1920, 1924- 1926
- Barbers - Journeymen Barbers' International Union, 1902-1920 (Box 27, Folder 73)
  1902, 1905, 1920
- Bill Posters - International Alliance of Bill Posters and Billers, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 74)
- Blacksmiths - International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 75)
- Bookbinders - International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 1918-1924 (Box 27, Folder 76)
  1918, 1921, 1924
- Boot and Shoe Workers - Boot and Shoe Workers Union, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 77)
- Brewery Workers - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal and Soft Drink Workers of America, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 78)
- Brick and Clay Workers - United Brick and Clay Workers of America, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 79)
- Bricklayers - Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union of America, 1920-1924 (Box 27, Folder 80)
  1920, 1922, 1924
- Bridge Structural and Iron Workers - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1915-1925 (Box 27, Folder 81)
  1915, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1925
- Machinery, Safe Movers and Riggers - Chicago, IL, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 82)
- Bridge Structural and Iron Workers - Dallas, TX, 1913-1918 (Box 27, Folder 83)
  1913, 1914, 1918
- Broom and Whisk Workers - International Broom and Whisk Makers Union, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 84)
- Building Trades - New York, NY, 1910-1919 (Box 27, Folder 85)
  1910, 1911, 1919
- RR Sleeping Car Conductors - Order of Sleeping Car Conductors, 1918-1922 (Box 27, Folder 86)
- Carpenters - Newark, NJ, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 87)
- Carpenters - New York, 1904 (Box 27, Folder 88)
- Carpenters - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 89)
- Cigar Workers - Cigarmakers' International Union, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 90)
- RR Dining Car Conductors - Brotherhood of Dining Car Conductors, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 91)
- Carriage and Wagon Workers - n/a, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 92)
- RR Carmen - Brotherhood of Railway Carmen, 1917-1921 (Box 27, Folder 93)
- Post Office Clerks - National Federation of Post Office Clerks, 1919-1923 (Box 27, Folder 94)
- RR Clerks - n/a, 1919-1922 (Box 27, Folder 95)
- Retail Clerks - Retail Clerks International Protective Association, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 96)
- Clothing Workers - Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 97)
- Hat Makers - United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 98)
- Contractors - Washington D.C., 1911 (Box 27, Folder 99)
- Coopers - Coopers International Union, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 100)
- Cutting Die Makers - International Union of Cutting Die and Cutter Makers, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 101)
- Diamond Workers - Diamond Workers Protective Union, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 102)
- Draftsmen - n/a, 1919-1923 (Box 27, Folder 103)
- Elevator Constructor - International Union of Elevator Constructors, 1916-1924 (Box 27, Folder 104)
- Engineers - American Association of Engineers, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 105)
- Engineers - International Union of Steam and Operating Engineers, 1920-1926 (Box 27, Folder 106)
  1920, 1922, 1926
- RR Engineers - International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1904-1921 (Box 27, Folder 107)
  1904, 1918, 1921
- Engineers - National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1919-1923 (Box 27, Folder 108)
- RR Enginemen - United Enginemen's Association, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 109)
- RR Expressmen - Order of Railway Expressmen, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 110)
- Fire Fighters - International Association of Fire Fighters, 1918-1923 (Box 27, Folder 111)
- RR Firemen and Enginemen - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1916-1923 (Box 27, Folder 112)
  1916, 1923
- Firemen and Oilers - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1919-1924 (Box 27, Folder 113)
- Food Workers - Amalgamated Food Workers, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 114)
- Fur Workers - International Fur Workers Union, 1920-1923 (Box 27, Folder 115)
- Ladies Garment Workers - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 116)
- Glass Bottle Blowers - Bottle Blowers' Association, 1919-1923 (Box 27, Folder 117)
- United Garment Workers - United Garment Workers of America, 1918-1923 (Box 27, Folder 118)
- Glass Workers - American Flint Glass Workers Union, 1919-1923 (Box 27, Folder 119)
- Window Workers - National Window Glass Workers, 1917-1923 (Box 27, Folder 120)
- Glove Workers - International Glove Workers Union, 1903-1916 (Box 27, Folder 121)
  1903, 1916
- Granite Cutters - Granite Cutters International Association of America, 1912-1921 (Box 27, Folder 122)
- Hatters - United Hatters of North America, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 123)
- Hod Carriers and Building Laborers - International Hod Carriers and Building Laborers Union, 1906-1923 (Box 27, Folder 124)
- Horseshoers - International Union of Horseshoers of the United States and Canada, 1918-1923 (Box 27, Folder 125)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees - Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1919-1923 (Box 27, Folder 126)
- Industrial Workers of the World - Industrial Workers of the World, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 127)
- The Workers' International Industrial Union - The Workers' International Industrial Union, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 128)
- Iron, Steel and Tin Workers - Amalgamated Association of Iron, Steel and Tin Workers of North America, 1919-1923 (Box 27, Folder 129)
- Jewelry Workers - International Jewelry Workers Union, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 130)
- National Association of Post Office Laborers - National Association of Post Office Laborers, 1913 (Box 27, Folder 131)
- Lace Workers - Chartered Society of the Amalgamated Lace Operative of America, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 132)
- Lathers - Wood, Wire and Metal Lathers' International Union, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 133)
- Laundry Workers - Laundry Workers International Union, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 134)
- Leather Workers - United Leather Workers International Union, 1917-1920 (Box 27, Folder 135)
- Rural Letter Carriers - National Federation of Rural Letter Carriers, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 136)
- Letter Carriers - National Association of Letter Carriers of the United States of America, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 137)
- Lithographers - Amalgamated Lithographers of America, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 138)
- Loyal Legion of Loggers and Lumbermen - Loyal Legion of Loggers and Lumbermen, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 139)
- Meat Cutters - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 140)
- Motive Power and Car Departments - Canadian National, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- RR Maintenance of Way - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1922-1923 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- RR Maintenance of Way - Louisville and Nashville, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Masters, Mates and Pilots - National Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots of America, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- RR Maintenance of Way - N/A, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Railway Mail - Railway Mail Association, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers - Western Federation of Miners, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Miners - United Mine Workers of America, 1920-1922 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- RR Mechanical Employees - Central NJ, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Machinists - International Association of Machinists, 1915-1921 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  1915, 1918, 1921
- Molders - International Molders Union of North America, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Musical Instrument Workers - Piano, Organ and Musical Instrument Workers International Union, 1911 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Musicians - American Federation of Musicians, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- One Big Union - n/a, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Oil Field Workers - International Association of Oil Field, Gas Well and Refinery Workers of America, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Paper Makers - International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Paper Mill Workers - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Pattern Workers - Pattern Makers' League of North America, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Paving Cutters - International Paving Cutters Union, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Post Office Employees - National Alliance of Postal Employees, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Painters - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Pharmacists - American Registered Pharmacists, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Photo Engravers - International Photo Engravers Union of North America, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Plate Printers - International Plate Printers and Die Stampers Union of North America, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Plasterers - Operative Plasterers' and Cement Finishers' International Association, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Plumbers - United Association of Journeymen, Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Potters - National Brotherhood of Operative Potters, 1914 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Powder Workers - United Powder and High Explosive Workers of America, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Pressmen - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union of North America, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Printers - Denver, CO, 1912-1916 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Quarry Workers - Quarry Workers International Union of North America, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- RR Administration - n/a, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- RR Workers - American Federation of Railroad Workers, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- RR Conductors - Order of Railway Conductors of America, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Roofers - United Slate, Tile and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers Association, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Sawmakers - Sawmakers' Union, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Seamen - International Seamen's Union of America, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- Sheet Metal Workers - Sheet Metal Workers International Union, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Shoe Workers - Shoe Workers Protective Union, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Shoe Workers - United Shoe Workers of America, 1909 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- RR Signalmen - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Spinners - International Spinners Union of America, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- RR Supervisors - International Association of Railroad Supervisors of Mechanics, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 43)
- Steam, Shovel and Dredge Men - International Brotherhood of Steam, Shovel and Dredge Men, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 44)
- Stereotypers - International Stereotypers and Electrotypers Union of North America, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- Stone Cutters - Journeymen Stone Cutters Association of North America, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 46)
- Curb Stone Cutters and Setters - Detroit, MI, 1916-1928 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  1916, 1923, 1924, 1928
- Blue Stone Cutters, Flaggers and Bridge and Curb Setters of America - New York, NY, 1911-1915 (Box 28, Folder 48)
- Stone Mounters - Stone Mounters' International Union, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 49)
- Street and Electric Railway Workers - Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway Employees of America, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 50)
- Switchmen - Switchmen's Union of North America, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 51)
- Tailors - Journeymen Tailors' Union of America, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 52)
- Teachers - American Federation of Teachers, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 53)
- Teamsters - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 54)
- RR Telegraphers - Order of the Railroad Telegraphers, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 55)
- Commercial Telegraphers Union of America - n/a, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 56)
- Textile Workers - United Textile Workers of America, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 57)
- Textile Operatives - American Federation of Textile Operatives, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 58)
- Textile Workers - Amalgamated Textile Workers of America, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 59)
- State Federation of Labor - Texas, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 60)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 61)
- Timber Workers - International Union of Timber Workers, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 62)
- Train Dispatchers - American Train Dispatchers Association, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 63)
- RR Trainmen - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 64)
- Tobacco Workers - Tobacco Workers International Union, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 65)
- Tunnel and Subway Construction - Tunnel and Subway Constructors International Union of North America, 1910 (Box 28, Folder 66)
- Typographical - International Typographical Union, 1917-1925 (Box 28, Folder 67)
  1917, 1924, 1925